Below the city of lights exists a world of darkness.
Catacombs is a horror, thriller film directed by David Elliot.
A young woman in Paris goes to a party in the enormous
labyrinth of limestone tunnels beneath Paris.
When she becomes separated from her friends, she is convinced
something is chasing her through the dark tunnels.
Victoria, played by Shannyn Sossamon.
Carolyn, played by P!nk.
Jean-Michel, played by Mihai Stănescu.
Henry, played by Emil Hostina.
Llaves, played by Sandi Dragoi.
Hugo, played by Cabral Ibacka.
Catacombs is a 2007 American horror film directed by Tomm Coker and
David Elliot, starring Shannyn Sossamon and Alecia Moore.
The plot follows a young woman attempting to find her way out of
the Catacombs of Paris with a killer pursuing her.
It is the first original film from FEARnet, collaborating with Lions
Gate Entertainment and was released on October 7, 2007.
The film's soundtrack was composed by Yoshiki, including the theme song
"Blue Butterfly" written by Yoshiki and performed by Violet UK.
The tone is dark and intense.